affle.com 2019-12-25

# About Affle | Consumer Focused Mobile Advertising | Mobile Marketing

## Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices of Affle. This privacy notice applies to information collected through advertisements delivered and/or processed through Affle’s platforms. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What information is collected from you through the advertisements/ Cookies/ SDKs, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of information collected as mentioned above.
  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use and Sharing**

We i.e. Affle collect information including your IP address (which provides broad location information as well), device type and model, system language, the device's operating system (such as Android or iOS), SDK version, mobile carrier name, mobile browsers installed on the device (such as Chrome or Safari), using either cookies or through the HTML headers when you view/ click on our ads. In addition, through the apps/ sites we partner with, we may get additional information regarding downloads and installations of mobile applications and information regarding in-app events (such as in-app purchases), and identifiers assigned to your device, such as its iOS Identifier for Advertising (IDFA), Android Advertising ID etc.

We may also collect / have access to such information that you have voluntarily shared with us through any forms submitted or collected during direct contact with you. We will not sell or rent the contents of information collected, to anyone.

Affle uses the above information in order to serve targeted advertising and offers and/or detect ad fraud. Affle does not use sensitive personal data such as race, religion, health or political views for interest based targeting.

We will use your information only for the purpose  stated above. We will not share your information with any third party outside our organization, except with authorized Data Processing partners who would have Privacy Policies similar to ours.

Unless specifically denied/ restricted, we may contact you via email in the future to update you about specials, new products, services, or any change in this Privacy Notice. We may use the data analytics from the data collected.

Read the detailed cookie policy [here](https://affle.com/cookie-policy)

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can contact us via email ([dpo@affle.com](mailto:dpo@affle.com)) or phone number as provided on our website, for any of the following:

  * **Right to Access Data-** Ask what information we have about you, if any.
  * **Right to Request Rectification-** Change/correct any information we have about you.
  * **Right to Erase-** Request for deleting any of your information that we have.
  * **Right to express concern** \- Express any concern you have about our use of your information.
  * **Right to restrict processing** \- Request to stop using your information/ data.
  * **Right to data portability-** You will be provided personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine- readable form

Affle reserves the right to share the information where required by law; such as to comply with a subpoena or requested by a Court of law of competent jurisdiction, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

**Security**

We will take all necessary measures to protect your information. When you share information, we ensure that your information is protected both online and offline.

Whenever, we collect information, that information is transmitted to us in an encrypted format and the same can be verified by a lock icon in the address bar or by “https” at the beginning of the address of the Web page.

While we use encryption to protect information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only those employees who are assigned with the job shall be granted access to information. However, no human has access to any individual user information, and only aggregated information and reports are provided to our internal employees or Affiliates on a strictly need basis. Individual user information is only stored in computers/ servers,  which are kept in a secure environment.

Affle is committed to implementing appropriate technical and organizational measures to safeguard Personal Data and ensure that all personnel who have access to and/or process Data are obliged to keep the Personal Data confidential.

Affle complies with its obligations under the Data Protection Legislation (GDPR) or any other applicable Data Protection Law/ Regulation by providing an adequate level of protection to any Personal Data that is transferred.
